(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ガチ愛してもいいんだよ？
きゅんきゅん生誕祭
SAKURAMIKO BIRTHDAY LIVE 2024
Is it okay to truly love me?
Kyun Kyun Birthday Festival
SAKURAMIKO BIRTHDAY LIVE 2024
NOW LOADING...
さくらみこ
エリートで誇らしすぎる巫女アイドル☆
Sakura Miko
The elite and overly proud shrine maiden idol☆
天音かなた
天使の握力50キロで君の心もわしづかみ♡
Amane Kanata
Grabbing your heart with an angel's 50kg grip♡
雪花ラミィ
お酒の大好きな雪の一族の令嬢
Yukihana Lamy
The snow-clan lady who loves alcohol
猫又おかゆ
信仰者が多い全肯定してくれるメス猫様♡
Nekomata Okayu
The lady cat with many followers who affirms all♡
桃鈴ねね
小学生男児の心を持つ元気いっぱいな女の子
Momosuzu Nene
A high-energy girl with the heart of a boy
AZKi
あなたの心をゼロゲッターしてくる歌姫
The songstress who 'zero-gets' your heart
湊あくあ
引きこもりがちのゲーマーメイド
Minato Aqua
The shut-in gamer maid
しぐれうい (9)
ロリコンを粛清する神出鬼没のロリ
Shigure Ui (9)
The elusive loli who purges lolicon
白上フブキ
実は恥ずかしがり屋なオタクすぎるケモミミ狐
Shirakami Fubuki
A shy, otaku beast-eared fox
うーあーもー
Ugh, ah, geez...
はい！
Okay!
やだやだミスってらんないね？
No, no, I can't afford to mess up, right?
にゃっはろー！さくらみこ生誕祭2024！
Nyahhalo! Sakura Miko Birthday Live 2024!
ベイピーダンス
Baby Dance
みんな、たくさんきゅんきゅんして楽しんでいってね！
Everyone, get your hearts fluttering and enjoy the show!
いくぞー！
Here we go!
真っ赤なハート差し出して
Hold out your deep red heart,
…そんなのやっぱ妄想じゃん
...but that's just a delusion after all.
そっちはどう思ってるの
What do you think over there?
いいかけて仕舞う無理みたい
I'm about to say it but stop, it seems impossible.
こんなんじゃ…って分かってるんだ
I know it shouldn't be like this...
本当にはまっていくんだ
I'm truly falling for you.
頑張りたい、あたしみたい
I want to try my best, just like me.
ぎゅーだってしたいかも
I might even want a hug.
カモン！
Come on!
ちょっとは変われていますか？
Have I changed even just a little?
足りないとこばっかだけど
I'm full of shortcomings, though.
ポンコツでドジなあたしだったら
If it's clumsy and klutzy old me,
きみはだめだよね？
you wouldn't like that, right?
でも　やだやだミスってらんない
But no, no, I can't afford to mess up.
やだやだ踊ってベイピーダンス
No, no, dance the Baby Dance.
あたしはまだ諦めない
I'm not giving up yet.
でもでも全然だめかも
But, but, it might be totally hopeless.
だってベイピーダンス　上手くできないの
'Cause the Baby Dance, I can't do it well.
だってベイピーダンス　伝えられないの
'Cause the Baby Dance, I can't convey it.
もっと可愛くなりたいのに
I want to be even cuter,
どうしたらいいとかわかんないし
but I don't know what I should do.
やだやだミスってらんないね？
No, no, I can't afford to mess up, right?
あーやっちまった　こんなはずじゃ
Ah, I blew it. It wasn't supposed to be like this.
どうして　どうして　分かっているのに
Why, oh why, even though I know...
見せたくないとこ透けちゃって
The parts I don't want to show show through.
無理無理　でも期待をしたいな
No way, no way. But I want to have hope.
いいですか？
Is that okay?
ポンコツもドジも全部あたしなんだよ
Being clumsy and a klutz, it's all part of me.
ちゃんと見ていてほしい
I want you to look at me properly.
ねえ、もう　やだやだくずって後悔
Hey, geez. No, no, crumbling and regretting.
やだやだ回ってベイピーダンス
No, no, spin around, Baby Dance.
だめなあたし塗り替えたい
I want to repaint the 'no-good' me.
でもでも全然だめかも
But, but, it might be totally hopeless.
だってベイピーダンス　上手くできないの
'Cause the Baby Dance, I can't do it well.
だってベイピーダンス　伝えられないの
'Cause the Baby Dance, I can't convey it.
もっと可愛くなりたいのに
I want to be even cuter,
どうしたらいいとかわかんないし
but I don't know what I should do.
まだ　まだ　いけるかな
I wonder if I can still, still do it.
まだ　まだ　言えるかな
I wonder if I can still, still say it.
まだ　まだ　できるかな
I wonder if I can still, still make it happen.
まだ　まだ　うぅ
Still, still, ugh...
ポンコツでドジでだめで足りないとこばっかだって
Even if I'm clumsy, a klutz, no good, and full of shortcomings...
きっとやめないんだ
I surely won't stop.
ポンコツでドジでだめで足りないとこばっかって
Being clumsy, a klutz, no good, and full of shortcomings...
見ていてほしい
I want you to watch me.
Uh yeah~
ねえ！
Hey!
やだやだミスってらんない
No, no, I can't afford to mess up.
やだやだ踊ってベイピーダンス
No, no, dance the Baby Dance.
あたしはまだ諦めない
I'm not giving up yet.
ほらほら全然だめじゃない
Look, look, it's not totally hopeless.
だってベイピーダンス　上手くできるから
'Cause the Baby Dance, I can do it well.
だってベイピーダンス　伝えられるから
'Cause the Baby Dance, I can convey it.
もっと可愛くなりたいから
Because I want to be even cuter,
どんな時だってそう頑張れるし
I can try my best no matter when.
だってベイピーダンス　きみに届くまで
'Cause the Baby Dance, until it reaches you.
だってベイピーダンス　きみに会えるまで
'Cause the Baby Dance, until I can meet you.
もっと可愛くなりたいから
Because I want to be even cuter,
どんな時だってそう頑張れるし
I can try my best no matter when.
やだやだミスってらんないね？
No, no, I can't afford to mess up, right?
はい！みんなにゃっはろー！
Okay! Nyahhalo, everyone!
エリートみこアイドル、さくらみこでーす！
Elite Miko Idol, Sakura Miko here!
さくらみこ、きゅんきゅん生誕祭2024に来てくれてありがとう！ちょっと噛んだ！
Thank you for coming to Sakura Miko's Kyun Kyun Birthday Live 2024! I stumbled over my words a bit!
はい、ということで、今回のライブはみんなを「きゅんきゅん」させる、可愛いライブとなっておりまーす！
Alright, so this live show is going to be a 'cute' performance that'll make everyone's hearts skip a beat!
ステージも見て！かわいい！あのね、すごい凝ってくれました、スタッフさんありがとう！
Look at the stage too! It's so cute! You know, they put a lot of work into it, thank you, staff members!
めちゃくちゃ街並みが、あの、とてもね、お洒落になっております。可愛い！
The cityscape is, well, it's become very stylish. So cute!
ツイートでポストしてくださいね！
Please post your tweets!
後半にはなんと
In the second half, there's even...
可愛い新衣装もあるのね
a cute new costume!
最後まで絶対見逃すなよ！
Don't miss it until the very end!
それでは
And now...
次はゲストパートです！
next is the guest part!
行くぞ！
Let's go!
みこち〜！ねえねえ！
Mikochi! Hey, hey!
あの人たちねねたちのこと見てな〜い？
Aren't those people looking at us?
いや、ねねのことだけ見てるかも〜
No, maybe they're only looking at Nene~
いやいやいやいや、勘違いすんなって！
No no no no, don't get the wrong idea!
みこのこと見てるもん！
They're looking at Miko!
はいはい〜おこちゃまは黙ってな〜
Yeah, yeah~ Kids should keep quiet~
ねえねえ、ねねといっしょにあそぶ？
Hey, hey, want to play with Nene?
みことあそぶよね？
You'll play with Miko, right?
わざとあざとエキスパート
Calculated, Cute Expert
なんでいつもそっけないのよ
Why are you always so cold?
クール気取っちゃって
Acting all cool
会いたいでしょ？恋しいでしょ？
You want to see me, right? You miss me, right?
素直になろうよ！
Let's be honest!
それなら君の気を引いちゃいます
Then I'll grab your attention
ドキドキ溢れる大作戦♡
A heart-pounding grand operation♡
1分 2分 3分 4分
1 min, 2 min, 3 min, 4 min
LINEも未読スルー＝するんだ
I'll even leave your LINE on 'unread'
「最近なんか気になって仕方ないんだよなー…」
"Lately I've been so interested in them, I can't help it..."
そんな感じで毎晩ずっと
Like that every night, all the time
何度も何度もきっと
Surely over and over
SNSしちゃうチェックでしょ？
You'll be checking my SNS, right?
ほら！もっと夢中になって！
Look! Get even more obsessed!
わざとあげた このストーリー
I posted this story on purpose
君の足跡チェックするの
Checking your footprint
あざといなんて言わないで
Don't say I'm calculated
だって Love you, Love you, Love you 好きだっちゃ！
Because Love you, Love you, Love you, I love you!
わざと遅い 既読通知
The read notification is late on purpose
私の心 非公開
My heart is 'private'
鍵をかけた 恋心
Locked away love
ねえ ほら ほら ほら
Hey, look, look, look
私を気にして もっともっと
Notice me more and more
私の声で 君が笑うから
Because you laugh at my voice
その瞬間も切り取って
I want to cut out that moment
即保存しちゃいたい
And save it immediately
そのために心奪っちゃいます
For that, I'll steal your heart
明日は君の誕生日
Tomorrow is your birthday
5分 4分 3分 2分
5 min, 4 min, 3 min, 2 min
「おめでとう！」わざと早まって
"Happy Birthday!" I said it early on purpose
「ごめん、誰より早く伝えたかったんだ」
"Sorry, I wanted to tell you before anyone else"
そんなこと言えばあっという間
If you say something like that, it's over in a flash
チョコレートみたい
Like chocolate
溶けちゃうね
It'll melt away
もう！早く振り向いて！
Jeez! Look at me already!
わざとあざと エキスパート
Calculated, Cute Expert
私の心 のぞいてよ
Take a peek into my heart
タイムラインは 君ばっか
My timeline is full of you
もっと Love you, Love you, Love you
More Love you, Love you, Love you
ドキドキキュンキュン！
Heart thumping!
君だけに 限定公開
Open only to you
足跡つくの 待ってるのに
Even though I'm waiting for your footprint
このままいけば ログアウト
If it goes on like this, I'll log out
そんなのやだ やだ やだ 私を愛して
I hate that, hate that, hate that, love me
ずっとずっと
Forever and ever
そっと見れた 君のアカウントも
Even your account that I took a peek at
やっぱ君も 私を好きなんだね
I knew it, you like me too
わざとは全部君の
Because all the "purposely"
ためなんだから
was for you
落ちちゃえばいいんだ
You should just fall for me
だけど私少し反省
But I'm reflecting a little
あまり試すの良くないね
It's not good to test you too much
やけに遅い 既読通知…
The read notification is awfully late...
やっぱ気になる！なる！
I knew it, I'm curious! Curious!
わざとあげた このストーリー
I posted this story on purpose
君の足跡チェックするの
Checking your footprint
あざといなんて 言わないで
Don't say I'm calculated
だって Love you, Love you, Love you 好きだっちゃ！
Because Love you, Love you, Love you, I love you!
わざと遅い 既読通知
The read notification is late on purpose
私の心 非公開
My heart is 'private'
鍵をかけた 恋心
Locked away love
ねえ ほら ほら ほら
Hey, look, look, look
私を気にして もっともっと
Notice me more and more
まさか君も わざとなの？
Could it be that you're doing it on purpose too?
みこち！お誕生日おめでとう！
Mikochi! Happy Birthday!
ねねちありがとう〜！
Nenechi, thank you~!
ライブ誘ってくれてありがとうね！
Thanks for inviting me to the live!
嬉しいよ！
I'm happy!
ううん、またママトクやろうね！
No problem, let's do Mamazoku again!
ちょっとちょっとみこ先輩！
Wait wait, Miko-senpai!
Wait, wait, Miko-senpai!
この祝い酒だぁ〜ってお酒飲みすぎなんですけどぉ！
You're drinking too much "celebratory sake"!
え〜そんなにみこの生誕祭が嬉しいのかなぁ〜？
Heh~ are you that happy about Miko's birthday?
あっ、めちゃくちゃ首振ってますよぉ！
Ah, she's shaking her head so much!
こら、ツンデレかぁ〜？
Hey, are you a tsundere?
こういうときは素直にならんかいっ
You should be honest at times like this!
そうだそうだぁ〜、ラミィたんいいこというなぁ〜！
Right, right~ Lamy-tan, you're saying good things!
おい、あれぇ〜？
Hey, huh?
ん？ちょっと！きいてんのかあ？
Hmm? Hey! Are you listening?
おねだりしてみてほしいの
I want you to try begging
ダーリン あなたは私の言うこと全然聞かない
Darling, you don't listen to me at all
あれほどやめてって言ったタバコもお酒も
The cigarettes and alcohol I told you to stop,
毎日二箱七合欠かさず
you still have two packs and seven go daily without fail.
肝臓やられてお釈迦になっても看病してあげないんだから
Even if your liver gives out and you pass away, I won't nurse you.
言いたいことは言わないし
You don't say what you want to say
行きたいとこからやりたいことまで
From where you want to go to what you want to do
決めてるくせしてだんまりさん
Even though you've decided, you're staying silent
ねえ そんなの馬鹿みたいじゃない？
Hey, isn't that just stupid?
そうじゃない？じゃない？じゃない？
Isn't it? Isn't it? Isn't it?
いつも思わせぶりな感じで
Always acting like you're hinting at something
察してほしい感じで
Acting like you want me to guess
わざと口にしないの ずるくない？
Isn't it unfair that you purposely don't say it?
馬鹿じゃないの？
Aren't you stupid?
お願いダーリン 見て聞いて
Please, Darling, look and listen
欲しいのは形のないもの
What I want is something without a form
馬鹿にしないで 見て聞いて
Don't make fun of me, look and listen
覗いてよ瞳の奥の方
Peer into the depths of my eyes
まっすぐ見つめて
Stare straight at me
おねだりしてみてほしいの？
Do you want me to try begging?
ダーリン 私はあなたの気持ちを全然知らないわ
Darling, I don't know your feelings at all
あれほど健気に見つめてきたのに今ではすっかり知らんぷり
Even though I've gazed at you so devotedly, now you ignore me.
ていうかそれって胡坐かいてるだけなんじゃないんですかぶっちゃけ
To be honest, aren't you just being complacent?
舌先三寸あなたのおかげで私のハートはボロボロです
Thanks to your glib tongue, my heart is in tatters.
つれない時はつれないし
When you're cold, you're cold
そっちが中々言い出さないから
Since you won't say anything
いつも私が舵取りじゃん？
I'm always the one taking the lead, right?
ねえ なんだか馬鹿みたいじゃない？
Hey, isn't it kind of stupid?
そうじゃない？じゃない？じゃない？
Isn't it? Isn't it? Isn't it?
どこか足元見てる感じで
Acting like you're looking down on me somewhere
値踏みされてる感じで
Acting like you're appraising me
駆け引きやら勝ち負けじゃなくない？
Isn't it not about tactics or winning and losing?
馬鹿じゃないの？
Aren't you stupid?
寡黙なダーリン 寝てないで
Silent Darling, don't sleep
切なさは飾りじゃないのよ
Pain isn't just a decoration
よそ見しないで 逃げないで
Don't look away, don't run away
触ってよ心の奥の方
Touch the depths of my heart
一瞬のことじゃない
It's not just for a moment
おねだりしてはくれないの？
Won't you beg for me?
言葉に出来ない臆病さは
The cowardice that can't be put into words
裸足で逃げたいのよ
I want to run away barefoot
甘えないでよ 口に出してよ
Don't be spoiled, say it out loud
もう ちゃんとこっち向いてったら
Geez, just turn this way properly
お願いダーリン 見て聞いて
Please, Darling, look and listen
欲しいのは形のないもの
What I want is something without a form
馬鹿にしないで 見て聞いて
Don't make fun of me, look and listen
覗いてよ瞳の奥の方
Peer into the depths of my eyes
寡黙なダーリン 寝てないで
Silent Darling, don't sleep
暴いてよ私の素顔を
Expose my true face
お願いダーリン そばにいて
Please, Darling, stay by my side
触らせて心の奥の方
Let me touch the depths of my heart
まっすぐ見つめて
Stare straight at me
おねだりしてみてほしいの
I want you to try begging
おねがいダーリン
Please, Darling
みこ先輩お誕生日おめでとー！
Miko-senpai, happy birthday!
ラミィたんありがとー！
Lamy-tan, thank you!
はぁ・・・誕生日なのに・・・
Sigh... even though it's my birthday...
どんなにみんなにお祝いされても結局部屋で一人なんだよなぁ。
No matter how much everyone celebrates, in the end, I'm alone in my room.
バーチャルって・・・。
Virtual life is...
あれ？
Huh?
かなたんからLINEだ
A LINE message from Kanatan
みこてんぱい、なに寂しがってるんですか？
Miko-tenpai, why are you feeling lonely?
かなたそがいるじゃん！
Kanataso is here for you!
わかるよその気持ち、
I understand that feeling,
だから・・・かなたそがなんでも聞いてあげるよ・・・？
So... Kanataso will listen to anything you have to say...?
かなたん・・・！♡
Kanatan...! ♡
インターネット最高 仮想と現実 仮定された有期交流燈の
Internet is the best, virtual and real, the assumed organic alternating light
かわいい虹色の照明です うい
is cute rainbow-colored lighting. Ui!
あらゆる透明なアカウントの複合体
A complex of all transparent accounts
このクソゴミカス
This piece of sh*t trash
キショキショな現実を忘れさせてあげる慈愛の天使
The angel of benevolence who will make you forget this creepy reality
大人のみんなには内緒だぞ
It's a secret from all the adults
大丈夫もう何も怖くないから
It's okay, because there's nothing to be afraid of anymore
こんなSNS抜け出して二人で海を見に行くぞ！
Let's escape this SNS and go see the ocean together!
インターネットやめろ！
Stop the internet!
みこ先輩、お誕生日おめでとう！
Miko-senpai, happy birthday!
ありがとぉ〜！
Thank you~!
イェイ！
Yay!
わかる真似をして
Pretending to understand
何も知らないね
You don't know anything
アナタ
You
何が悲しいの
What is sad?
何が寂しいの
What is lonely?
聴こえてる？
Can you hear me?
人が恋しくて
Longing for people
人がイヤすぎて
Hating people too much
ループ
Looping
夜が好き（なの）に
Even though I like the night
一人じゃ寒くて
It's cold being alone
震えてる
I'm shivering
本当は幸せを知っているのに
Even though I actually know happiness
不幸なフリ やめられないね
I can't stop pretending to be unhappy
アンチに負けず
Not losing to antis
信者に媚びず
Not pandering to believers
どんなに努力を重ねても
No matter how much effort I put in
一寸先は地獄行き
One step ahead is a trip to hell
いやもうすでに冥府魔道
No, it's already a demonic path to hell
地獄の沙汰もいいね次第
Even hell's judgment depends on likes
決死のトラップ蜘蛛の糸
A life-risking trap, a spider's thread
こんなに苦しいはずなのに
Even though it's supposed to be this painful
インターネットがやめられない！
I can't stop the internet!
駆け巡るエクスタシー
Ecstasy running through
溶けるマイスリー
Melting Myslee
画面光りだすの
The screen starts to glow
不安止まらないよ
My anxiety won't stop
誰か殺してくれ
Someone kill me
イヤだ死にたくない
No, I don't want to die
朝は見たくないの
I don't want to see the morning
ムリだ！
It's impossible!
死ぬ！
I'm dying!
アタマが割れていく
My head is splitting open
それでもわたしはこのカオスをオタクと歩む
Even so, I will walk through this chaos with my otaku
ここにしかない光景を見つけに行くから
Because I'm going to find a sight that can only be found here
あんなにおそろしい乱れたインターネットから
From such a terrifying, chaotic internet
この雪みたいに美しい電波がきたんだよ
Waves as beautiful as this snow came through
カウンセリングを受けたの
I received counseling
先生からネットをやめろって言われて
The doctor told me to stop using the internet
もうお前らと会えないと思った瞬間
The moment I thought I couldn't see you guys anymore
胸が苦しくて
My chest hurt
リアルが壊れても
Even if reality breaks
ココが良いって思ったの！
I thought, this place is better!
初めてフォローされた日のこと覚えてる？
Do you remember the day I was followed for the first time?
こんなわたしを見て
Looking at me like this
承認してくれた温もりって
The warmth of being recognized
もう細かいことはどうでもいいね
The details don't matter anymore, do they?
せーのっ
One, two...
インターネット最高！
Internet is the best!
きっと……
Surely...
キボンヌ！
I want!
半年ROMれ
Read for half a year
キタ！
It's here!
ツンデレよし！イチオシ！
Tsundere ok! Favorite!
久々にワロタ
LMAO for the first time in a while
コワイナ
How scary
これは乙じゃなくてポニーテールなんだからね
This isn't 'ots', it's a ponytail, okay?
腐女子 ぬるぽ ガッ！
Fujoshi Nurupo Gha!
発見伝！
Found it!
ういちゃ〜ん、へへへ。
Ui-chan~ Hehehe.
かわいいねぇ〜、ちっちゃいねぇ〜･･･
So cute~ So tiny...
キモイですよ、みこおねーちゃん＾＾
You're gross, Miko-oneechan.
お誕生日なのにお巡りさんに捕まりたいんですかぁ？
Do you want to get caught by the police on your birthday?
そんなこといって〜、みこのことお祝いしに来てくれたくせに〜
Saying that, even though you came to celebrate Miko's birthday~
はぁぁ、ま、一年警察のお世話にならないといいですね。
Haa, well, I hope you don't get in trouble with the police for a year.
Lonely ロリロリ神、降臨
Lonely Loli-kami, descent
鐘を鳴らせばこの通り
Ring the bell, and just like this
これは救済のレクイエム
This is a requiem of salvation
せーのっ
Ready, set, go!
触ったら逮捕！
Touch me and you're arrested!
獄中確定
Incarceration confirmed
ごめんなさーい
I'm sorry!
ごめんなさい
I'm sorry
聞こえなーい
I can't hear you!
粛聖!! ロリ神レクイエム☆
Shukusei!! Loli-Kami Requiem☆
将来はお前なんかに好かれたくない
I don't want to be liked by someone like you in the future
泥水で口を洗え
Wash your mouth with muddy water
さーあーお
Sa-a-o
ね
Right?
さあ、おまわりさん
Now, Mr. Officer,
連れて行って
take them away.
妄想しか取り柄のない
Those who have nothing going for them but delusions,
かわいそうな人
such poor souls.
ういちゃん！ういちゃん！待ってよういちゃん！
Ui-chan! Ui-chan! Wait, Ui-chan!
その姿 親に見せられますか？
Can you show that appearance to your parents?
みこちゃん！みこちゃん！かわいいよぉー！
Miko-chan! Miko-chan! You're so cute!
わぁ、ありがとう。お疲れ様で～す^^
Wow, thank you. Good job out there! ^^
ロリロリ神降臨
The Loli-Loli God descends.
マジやば奴らに用心
Beware of the truly dangerous guys.
まともじゃないなら
If you're not normal,
はよ消えてください
please disappear quickly.
ロリロリ神降臨
The Loli-Loli God descends.
鐘を鳴らせばこの通り
If I ring the bell, just like this...
とても優しくて
A very kind and
素敵なお兄ちゃん
wonderful big brother.
楽園でほら
In paradise, see,
ねんねしな
go to sleep.
ほら、世の中にはこんなに気持ち悪い人たちがはびこっているんです。
See, the world is crawling with such creepy people.
みんなさらしてあげますよ！
I'll expose everyone!
さわったら逮捕！
Touch me and you're arrested!
獄中で点呼！
Roll call in prison!
いちにーさんしー！
One, two, three, four!
ごめんなさーい！
I'm sorry!
ハァ？
Hah?
ごめんなさいが聞こえない！
I can't hear your "I'm sorry"!
粛聖！ロリ神レクイエム
Judgment! Lolikami Requiem
はぁーい！獄中にいる皆しゃーん！
Hello! Everyone in prison!
刑務所ファンミーティングのお時間でーす！
It's time for the prison fan meeting!
その腐りきった耳をゴリゴリかぽじって
Scrub out those rotten ears of yours
よぉーく聴いてくださいね。
and listen very carefully.
助かる～ 助かる～ 助かる～
This helps... This helps... This helps...
お兄ちゃん お姉ちゃん
Big brother, big sister.
もう希望もない ゴミだおめーら
You're already beyond hope. You're just trash.
汚物消毒110番！
Filth disinfection, dial 110!
固有結界、はっつ、どーお！
Reality Marble, activate!
粛聖！
Judgment!
ういビーム！
Ui-Beam!
嗚呼、この世の醜さを
Ah, the ugliness of this world...
集めて描いてみるよ
I'll try to gather and paint it.
真っ白なキャンバスが
The pure white canvas
穢れて泣いている
is stained and weeping.
Lonely 振り向いた少女は
Lonely, the girl who looked back
そっと手を掴む
softly grabs your hand.
「楽園など無いから」
"Because there is no paradise."
おっきなお友達の皆へ
To all my big friends,
お前らが打ち込んでいる虚無には
in the void you are plunging into,
何の意味があるの？
what meaning is there?
ねえ、教えてよ。
Hey, tell me.
みこ、ぜんぜーんわかんないんだ！
Miko doesn't understand at all!
レクイエム
Requiem
本当に気持ち悪い。
Truly disgusting.
みこちゃん、お誕生日おめでとう！
Miko-chan, happy birthday!
ありがとう！ういちゃん、このあとご飯...
Thank you! Ui-chan, let's go eat after this...
フブさんフブさん、なんかここ変な怖い感じがするんですけど...
Fubu-san, Fubu-san, I feel a strange, scary vibe here...
いやあ、さすがみこさん！巫女さんなだけに、ちゃんと感じるんだね～。
Whoa, as expected of Miko-san! Just as a shrine maiden should, you can sense it, huh?
ここ、実はやばいんですよ。
This place is actually dangerous, you know.
フブさん、みこ誕生日なんですけどぉ！
Fubu-san, it's Miko's birthday, you know!
まあまあ白上がいるし、大丈夫ですよ！
Now, now, Shirakami is here, so it's okay!
それに...いざという時は、守ってくれる人もいますし、ねっ？
Besides... if push comes to shove, there's someone to protect us, right?
ねえねえ もしも の もしも だよ？
Hey, hey, what if, just what if?
私が帰り道 グリズリーに襲われたら
If on my way home, I was attacked by a grizzly bear,
あなたならどうする？
what would you do?
もしものもしもだよ あなたはどうする？
What if, just what if? What would you do?
グリズリーに襲われたら♡
作詞・作曲 滝口有人
If I'm Attacked by a Grizzly Bear ♡
Lyrics & Composition: Arihito Takiguchi
もしもね
If, you know,
帰り道
on the way home,
グリズリーと出会って
I met a grizzly bear,
暗闇で目が合えば
and our eyes met in the dark,
恐怖で動けないわ
I wouldn't be able to move from fear.
震える唇で
With trembling lips,
助けてと電話したら
if I called for help,
貴方はすぐに
would you immediately
来てくれますか？
come to my side?
ねえ 嘘付きって
Hey, as a liar,
あしらわないで
don't brush me off.
真実なの
It's the truth,
お願い
please.
パジャマだって駆けつけてね
Even in your pajamas, please rush over.
1秒を争うのよ
Every second counts.
Yシャツに着替える間に
In the time it takes to change into a shirt,
骨まで食べられちゃうわ
I'll be eaten down to my bones.
裸足だって駆けつけてね
Even barefoot, please rush over.
私を疑う前に
Before you doubt me,
心配でたまらなくて
I'm so worried I can't stand it,
走り出してほしいのです
I want you to start running.
そんな人が嬉しいの
I'd be happy with someone like that.
もしもね
If, you know,
曲がり角
at a street corner,
グリズリーにぶつかり
I bumped into a grizzly bear,
物陰で向き合えば
and we faced each other in the shadows,
怖くて叫べないわ
I'd be too scared to scream.
震える左手で
With my trembling left hand,
助けてとメールしたら
if I texted for help,
貴方はすぐに
would you immediately
見てくれますか？
look for me?
ねえ ほら吹きって
Hey, as a teller of tall tales,
片付けないで
don't dismiss me.
本当なの
It's true,
信じて
believe me.
仕事だって駆けつけてね
Even from work, please rush over.
何もかもを投げ出して
Tossing everything aside.
残業が終わるまでに
Before overtime is over,
ほら丸飲みされちゃうわ
look, I'll be swallowed whole.
どこにだって駆けつけてね
Please rush to wherever I am.
私を疑う前に
Before you doubt me,
いてもたってもいられない
I can't just stand still,
取り乱してほしいのです
I want you to lose your composure.
そんな人が愛しいの
I adore someone like that.
ねえ、もしもし！大変大変！
Hey, hello! It's a disaster!
帰り道にグリズリーがいるの！
There's a grizzly on the way home!
助けて、私、怖くて一歩も動けないよ！
Help me, I'm too scared to move a single step!
今すぐ来て助けて！
Come right now and help!
きゃー、こっちに来るよー！
Aah, it's coming this way!
私のこと見てるし！きゃー！
It's looking at me! Aah!
助けてよー！おーねーがーいー！
Help us! Pleeaaase!
ねえ 嘘付きって
Hey, as a liar,
あしらわないで
don't brush me off.
真実なの
It's the truth,
お願い
please.
パジャマだって駆けつけてね
Even in your pajamas, please rush over.
1秒を争うのよ
Every second counts.
Yシャツに着替える間に
In the time it takes to change into a shirt,
骨まで食べられちゃうわ
I'll be eaten down to my bones.
裸足だって駆けつけてね
Even barefoot, please rush over.
私を疑う前に
Before you doubt me,
心配でたまらなくて
I'm so worried I can't stand it,
走り出してほしいのです
I want you to start running.
そんな人が嬉しいの
I'd be happy with someone like that.
貴方しかいないの
There's only you.
ありがとう
Thank you
みこさん、今日はお誕生日おめでとう！
Miko-san, happy birthday today!
ありがとう、フブさん！
Thank you, Fubu-san!
グリズリーじゃないけど、キツネが食べちゃうぞ！
I'm not a grizzly, but this fox is gonna eat you up!
う、う、にげなー！
U-u- Run away!
超めてたいソング
～こんなに幸せでいいのかな？～
Super Auspicious Song
~Is It Okay to Be This Happy?~
Ohめでたい！ おめでたい！ 超めでたい！
Oh celebratory! It's celebratory! Super celebratory!
小めでたいっ 中めでたい？ おめでたい！
Small celebratory! Medium celebratory? It's celebratory!
本日、ハレの日、
Today is a lucky day,
雨でもハレ
clear even if it rains.
一生に一度のエブリデイ
A once-in-a-lifetime everyday,
だけどやっぱり今日はスペシャル
but today is special after all.
本日の衣装は悩みません
I won't worry about today's outfit.
一周回ってシンプルなジグ
Going full circle, it's a simple jig,
だけどあれ？でもやっぱ派手すぎ？
but wait? Is it too flashy after all?
来年の今は記念日
This time next year will be an anniversary.
...み
...mi
それまではたくさんもっと
Until then, more and more
どーでもいいことと貯金をしましょう
Let's save up even the trivial things
そして大事なこと
And the important thing
まずはトゥデイをブチ上げよ？
First, let's blow up today?
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
私こんなに幸せでいいのかな？
Is it okay for me to be this happy?
本当はそんなこと悩んでないけど
I'm not actually worried about that, though
だってちょっとくらいのマイナスもなきゃ
Because if there isn't a bit of negative...
って思うくらいいい感じ
...I feel it's just that good
まぁねこんなに幸せでいいのです
Well, it's fine to be this happy
だってわたし自分で選んだんだから
Because I chose this myself
いぬはかけまわり
Dogs run around
ねこはかわいいし
Cats are cute
青い鳥は飛ぶ
Blue birds fly
みんながいる！
Everyone is here!
当日サケの日、普通に良い
The actual day is Salmon Day, just fine
一生で一番ヤングな日だけど仕方ないです
It's the youngest day of my life, but that can't be helped
って感じで冷めたりもしてるよ
I'm feeling cool about it like that
サプライズのメッセージ驚くはずないお決まり
Surprise messages, I won't be surprised, it's a given
一昨年の今は他人で
Two years ago today we were strangers
それまではたくさんもっと
Until then, more and more
無駄かもってことと恋愛をしたね
I did things that might be wasteful, and fell in love
だけど大事なこと
But the important thing...
今は本当に大好きです
...is now I really love you
おめでとう！私こんなに幸せでいいのかな？
Congratulations! Is it okay for me to be this happy?
本当はそんなこと心配ないけど
I'm not actually worried about that, though
だってちょっとくらいの試練とかもなきゃ
Because if there aren't a bit of trials...
って思うくらいいい感じ
...I feel it's just that good
結局幸せでいいのです
In the end, it's fine to be happy
だってわたしちゃんと戦ったんだから
Because I fought properly
おみこしにのって
Riding on a portable shrine
花火もあげて
Launching fireworks
いいこと全部一度にしよう！
Let's do all the good things at once!
おめでとう！私こんなに幸せでいいのかな？
Congratulations! Is it okay for me to be this happy?
本当はそんなこと悩んでないけど
I'm not actually worried about that, though
だってちょっとくらいのマイナスもなきゃ
Because if there isn't a bit of negative...
って思うくらいいい感じ
...I feel it's just that good
こんなに幸せでいいのです
It's fine to be this happy
だってわたし自分で選んだんだから
Because I chose this myself
いぬはかけまわり
Dogs run around
ねこはかわいいし
Cats are cute
青い鳥は飛ぶ　みんながいる
Blue birds fly, everyone is here
最高の今におめでとうだよ！
Congratulations to the best "now"!
Let's Have a Good time 今日はセレブレーション
Let's Have a Good time, today's a celebration
超めでたいじゃん もっとセレブレーション
It's super celebratory, more celebration
みこち〜！誕生日おめでとう、ゲッサーしてきちゃった♡
Mikochi~! Happy birthday, I came to play Geoguessr with you♡
衣装とってもかわいいね〜！ね？君もそう思うよね？
Your outfit is so cute~! Right? You think so too, don't you?
あずちゃん〜！ありがとう〜！えへへ〜
Az-chan~! Thank you~! Ehehe~
･･･ところで、プレゼントを持ってきたんだけど、つけてくれる？
...By the way, I brought a present, will you wear it?
え？プレゼント？
Eh? A present?
そう、ねこみみだにゃ〜！
Yes, cat ears nya~!
ええ！ねこみみ！？にゃ～～！
Ehh! Cat ears!? Nya~~!
猫になって甘やかされたい
I want to become a cat and be pampered
猫になって愛されたいよ
I want to become a cat and be loved
猫になってお昼寝させて
Let me become a cat and take a nap
起きたら100万登録いってないかな
I wonder if I'll have 1 million subscribers when I wake up
猫ならばいける！
If it's a cat, I can do it!
二度寝したいけどちゃんと
I want to sleep in, but...
おはようツイートしなくちゃ
...I have to do my proper "Good morning" tweet
下書き悩んで３時間たって
Three hours passed while worrying over the draft
完璧な１４０字
A perfect 140 characters
操作ミスってデリート
Then a misclick deletes it
心が折れる日曜日
Heart-breaking Sunday
Heartbreaking Sundays
休みもなしで歌い続ける
Singing endlessly without a break
そんなのへっちゃら余裕だぜ
That's no problem at all, easy-peasy
みんなと一緒なら大丈夫
If I'm with everyone, I'll be okay
うー
Ooh
だから応援よろしくね
So please keep supporting me
本質的に甘やかして
Pamper me to my core
配信毎回全編見てね
Watch every stream from start to finish
でも今日はやばい
But today is really tough
本当にねむい
I'm just so sleepy
こんなわたしもちゃんと見てほしい
I want you to see this side of me too
無償の愛がほしい
I want unconditional love
だから猫になって甘やかされたい
So I want to be a cat and be pampered
にゃー！
Nya!
猫になって愛されたいよ
I want to be a cat and be loved
にゃにゃー！
Nya nya!
猫になっておひるねさせて
Being a cat, let me take a nap
起きたら100万登録だ
When I wake up, I'll have a million subs
いける〜！ いけるぅ〜！
We can do it! I can do it~!
猫になって輝きたいの
I want to be a cat and shine
にゃー！
Nya!
猫になって開拓するよ
I'll pioneer new things as a cat
にゃにゃー！
Nya nya!
もっと君に伝わりますように
Hoping this reaches you even more
猫ならばいける
If I'm a cat, I can do it
お散歩してたら公園で かわいいワンちゃん見つけたよ
While out for a walk in the park, I found a cute doggie
撫でようとしたら吠えられた
When I tried to pet it, it barked at me
やっぱ猫になりたい
As I thought, I want to be a cat
でもどうすればいい？
But what should I do?
猫のなり方
How to become a cat
ググれど出ない 本だしてほしい
Searching Google finds nothing; please write a book about it
スクールつくってほしい
I wish someone would start a school for it
だから猫になって抱きしめられたい
So I want to be a cat and be hugged
にゃー！
Nya!
猫になってナデナデしてよ
Become a cat and pet me
にゃにゃー！
Nya nya!
猫になってエサを与えて
Being a cat, please feed me
山盛りチュールをよろしくね
Give me a heap of Churu, please
よろしくね
Please do
猫になって恋してたいの
I want to be a cat and be in love
にゃー！
Nya!
猫になって笑いあおうよ
Become a cat and let's laugh together
にゃにゃー！
Nya nya!
もっとみんな猫になろうよ
Let's all become cats more
にゃー
Nya
にゃにゃー！
Nya nya!
にゃー
Nya
にゃ
にゃー
Nya
にゃにゃにゃにゃー
Nya nya nya nya
にゃー
Nya
にゃにゃー！
Nya nya!
にゃー
Nya
にゃにゃにゃにゃにゃー
Nya nya nya nya nya
にゃー！
Nya!
本当やばい
This is really bad
起きたら12時
It was 12 o'clock when I woke up
ラインめちゃきてる
Getting so many LINE messages
でもまあ しょうがない
But well, it can't be helped
逆に二度寝しましょう
On the contrary, let's just go back to sleep
だから
So
だから猫になって甘やかされたい
So I want to be a cat and be pampered
にゃー！
Nya!
猫になって愛されたいよ
I want to be a cat and be loved
にゃにゃー！
Nya nya!
猫になっておひるねさせて
Being a cat, let me take a nap
起きたら100万登録だ
When I wake up, I'll have a million subs
いける〜！ いけるぅ〜！
We can do it! I can do it~!
猫になって輝きたいの
I want to be a cat and shine
にゃー！
Nya!
猫になって開拓するよ
I'll pioneer new things as a cat
にゃにゃー！
Nya nya!
もっと君に伝わりますように
Hoping this reaches you even more
もっともっと
More and more
猫になって甘やかされたい ずっとされたい
I want to be a cat and be pampered, always pampered
猫になって抱きしめられたい もっとられたい
I want to be a cat and be hugged, hugged even more
猫になって恋してたいの
I want to be a cat and be in love
にゃー！
Nya!
猫になって笑いあおうよ
Become a cat and let's laugh together
にゃにゃー！
Nya nya!
もっとみんな猫になろうよ
Let's all become cats more
猫ならばいける
If I'm a cat, I can do it
きみとならばいける
If I'm with you, I can do it
にゃー！
Nya!
みこち、お誕生日おめでとう！
Mikochi, happy birthday!
猫ならばいける歌えて嬉しかった！まったね〜！
I was so happy to sing 'Neko Nara Bai Keru'! See ya!
まったね〜！あずちゃんありがとね〜！
See ya! Thanks, Azu-chan!
みこち〜、お誕生日おめでとぉ〜。僕こうり〜ん
Mikochi~, happy birthday~. I have descended~
おかゆん！いや...全肯定的ネコサマおかゆん...！
Okayun! No... All-affirming Nekosama Okayun...!
よしよし、みこちはライブ頑張ってえらいえら〜い
There, there, Mikochi is so good for doing her best for the live
とってもエリートだよぉ〜
You're a total elite~
えへへ...エリートぉ〜？え、そうかなぁ〜？
Ehehe... Elite~? Eh, is that so~?
さすがおかゆん、わかってくれるんだねぇ〜
As expected of Okayun, you really understand me~
おーけーおーけー ぼくが君の 神様になったげる
Okay, okay, I'll become your god
お願い！お願い！
Please! Please!
しょうがないなー
I guess I have no choice
お願い！お願い！助けておかゆん！
Please! Please! Help me, Okayun!
悩める現代の皆様
To all you troubled people of today
けたたましい時代の真ん中
In the middle of this boisterous era
自分の事さえ
When even your own self
愛せない
You cannot love
そんなことありませんか？
Isn't that the case for you?
誰かに認めてもらいたいな
I want someone to recognize me
何も上手くいかずやだやだ
Nothing goes well, it's so annoying
神頼み それなのに
Godly favor, and yet...
どこに行ったら会えるの神様
Where can I go to meet you, God?
Help me!
どうしたのー？
What's wrong?
Help me!
うんうん
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Help me!
そっかー 大変だねー
I see, that's tough.
Save me!
でもねー
But you know,
大丈夫！
It's okay!
ぼくが味方でいるからさー
Because I'm on your side!
生きてるだけで満点
Just being alive is a perfect score.
＼満点！／
A perfect score!
自信持ちなよ全然
Have some confidence, absolutely.
＼全然！／
Absolutely!
信じていいよ当然
You should believe it, of course.
＼当然！／
Of course!
君はとっても素敵だよ！
You are very wonderful!
ありとあらゆるこの世の全てを
Everything and anything in this world...
肯定！肯定！肯定！肯定！
Affirm! Affirm! Affirm! Affirm!
全知全能全肯定！
Omniscience, omnipotence, total affirmation!
それって結構 神じゃない？
Isn't that pretty much like a God?
いいじゃん いいじゃん すごいじゃん
It's good, it's good, it's amazing.
＼すごい！／
Amazing!
いいじゃん いいじゃん えらいじゃん
It's good, it's good, you're doing great.
＼えらい！／
Great!
そです そです もっと自由に
That's right, that's right, more freely...
生きていいんだよ全肯定
You can live freely, total affirmation.
いいじゃん いいじゃん すごいじゃん
It's good, it's good, it's amazing.
＼すごい！／
Amazing!
いいじゃん いいじゃん えらいじゃん
It's good, it's good, you're doing great.
＼えらい！／
Great!
オーケー オーケー 君は最高
Okay, okay, you're the best.
何度だって伝えたげる
I'll tell you as many times as it takes.
お願い！お願い！
Please! Please!
しょうがないなー
I guess I have no choice.
お願い！お願い！助けておかゆん！
Please! Please! Help me, Okayun!
承認欲求マウント社会
A society of status-climbing and validation-seeking.
マイナス思考に自己否定
Negative thinking and self-denial.
誰もがみんな求め続ける
Everyone keeps searching for...
自分だけにある特別感
The special feeling that belongs only to them.
通知化されちゃう世知辛い時代
A tough era where everything is quantified.
いいね フォロワー 高評価
Likes, followers, high ratings.
そんなの全然必要ないよ
None of that is necessary at all.
僕の言葉に全て委ねて
Entrust everything to my words.
あーね！いいじゃん！うんうん！えらい！あー！
I see! Good! Uh-huh! Great! Ah!
完璧今日もお疲れ！
Perfect, good job today as well!
グッド！けっこう！肯定！肯定！
Good! Nice! Affirm! Affirm!
さすが自信持って！おかゆん！
As expected, have confidence! Okayun!
素晴らしい世界そばにいるよ
A wonderful world, I'll be by your side.
だいすき ちょうすき つまりすき！
I love you, I really love you, I just love you!
できるよ当然なんとかなるよ
You can do it, of course, it'll work out somehow.
にっこりぬくぬくねこ可愛がり
Smiling warmly, doting on the cat.
神様も人様も
Both gods and people...
なにもかも信じられなくても
...even if you can't believe in anything.
猫様を信じましょう
Let's believe in the Cat-sama.
甘えましょう 甘えましょう 安心
Let's be spoiled, let's be spoiled, peace of mind.
晴れの日も雨の日も
On sunny days and rainy days,
支えましょう君の心を
I will support your heart.
病める時 泣ける時
When you're sick, when you're crying,
ここに来たならもう大丈夫
Now that you're here, it's okay.
Help me! (はいはい) Help me! (よしよし)
Help me! (Yes, yes) Help me! (There, there)
Help me! (うんうん) 心配しないで
Help me! (Uh-huh) Don't worry.
Save me! (ほらね) Save me! (大丈夫！)
Save me! (See?) Save me! (It's okay!)
君もレッツおにぎゃー！
You too, let's Onigya!
いいじゃん いいじゃん すごいじゃん
It's good, it's good, it's amazing.
＼すごい！／
Amazing!
いいじゃん いいじゃん えらいじゃん
It's good, it's good, you're doing great.
＼えらい！／
Great!
そです そです もっと僕の
That's right, that's right, more by my...
側においでよ全肯定
...side, come here, total affirmation.
いいじゃん いいじゃん すごいじゃん
It's good, it's good, it's amazing.
＼すごい！／
Amazing!
いいじゃん いいじゃん えらいじゃん
It's good, it's good, you're doing great.
＼えらい！／
Great!
オーケー オーケー ぼくが君の
Okay, okay, I'll be your...
猫様になってあげる
...Cat-sama.
のんびりいこうよ ばっちりピカイチ
Let's take it easy, perfectly top-notch.
ファンタスティック へっちゃらポジティブ
Fantastic, carefree and positive.
まあまあみんな無理しないでね
Now, now, everyone, don't overdo it.
めっちゃ心配だよ おかゆん！
I'm so worried, Okayun!
もぐもぐ (おかゆー！) やっぱり (おかゆー！)
Mogu mogu (Okayu!) Just as I thought (Okayu!)
ゆきの！ (おかゆー！) よっしゃいくぞ！
Yukino! (Okayu!) Alright, let's go!
肯定！肯定！肯定！肯定！
Affirm! Affirm! Affirm! Affirm!
全知全能全肯定！
Omniscience, omnipotence, total affirmation!
いいじゃん いいじゃん すごいじゃん
It's good, it's good, it's amazing.
いいじゃん いいじゃん えらいじゃん
It's good, it's good, you're doing great.
さあさあ皆さん ご唱和ください！
Now, now, everyone, please sing along!
全知全能全肯定！
Omniscience, omnipotence, total affirmation!
いいじゃん いいじゃん すごいじゃん
It's good, it's good, it's amazing.
＼すごい！／
Amazing!
いいじゃん いいじゃん えらいじゃん
It's good, it's good, you're doing great.
＼えらい！／
Great!
オーケー オーケー 新世界の
Okay, okay, of the new world,
神様になってあげるー
I'll become your God!
お願い！お願い！らくにいこうよ
Please! Please! Let's take it easy.
お願い！お願い！良好るんるん！
Please! Please! Good vibes, run run!
お願い！お願い！レッツゴーららら！
Please! Please! Let's go, la la la!
お願い！お願い！笑ってこ！
Please! Please! Let's laugh!
みこち、お誕生日おめでとう！
Mikochi, happy birthday!
ありがとお！
Thank you!
まったねー！
See ya later!
うわあ！
Whoa!
おかゆん！
Okayun!
み、みこちゃん…お誕生日おめでと…
M-Miko-chan... Happy birthday...
あくたん！ありがとお〜！
Akutan! Thank you~!
なんでそんな端っこにいるの？
Why are you all the way over in the corner?
あくたんオオトリだよ！ほら、おいでぇ〜！
Akutan, you're the grand finale! Come on over!
も、もおしょーがないなぁ…
G-Good grief, I guess I have no choice...
み、みこちゃんもしかしてあていのこと好きすぎ…？
Miko-chan, could it be that you like me too much...?
よーしいくぞぉー！
Alright, let's gooo!
えっ、あ…あれぇ…？
Eh, ah... Huh...?
あいわな
I Wanna
I wanna!
ミュージック！
Music!
月曜日は体が動きません
On Mondays, my body won't move.
っていうか毎日でした。
Actually, it was every day.
ビリビリ偏頭痛
Tingling migraine.
あたしったら
As for me...
メイドのくせしてお料理ダメ
Even though I'm a maid, I'm bad at cooking.
掃除もちょっとアレ
Cleaning is also a bit of a...
てんてこ舞いで まいった
Dancing around, I'm beat.
うーん 精進あるのみですね
Hmm, I just have to keep working hard.
会いたくなってしまったな 今夜も
I've come to want to see you again tonight.
夜な夜な集まって何する？
What shall we do, gathering night after night?
月火水木金土日さ 365日
Mon, Tue, Wed, Thu, Fri, Sat, Sun - 365 days.
画面越し ご挨拶
Greetings through the screen.
せーの
One, two!
好きになっちゃったって言っちゃったって
Even if I say I've fallen in love,
ない！
No way!
勝手に凹んだって泣いてみたって 全然可愛くない
Even if I get depressed or try to cry, it's not cute at all.
君だって同じ ダメよりの人種です
You're the same, a hopeless kind of person.
そんな優しくして... あたしに気があるのかな？
Being so kind... are you interested in me?
賛成！
I agree!
もうこんな時間 どんな予感 神ハプニング
It's already this time, what a premonition, a god-tier happening.
ええ？
Eh?
ああ中毒症状 依存度マックス メンタル崩壊
Ah, addiction symptoms, dependency max, mental breakdown.
あなたのことを もっともっと知りたい
I want to know more and more about you.
あいわな
I wanna
みゅーじっく
Music
水曜日は意識がレボリューション
Wednesday is a revolution of consciousness.
っていうか毎日でした。
Actually, it was every day.
ビリビリ偏頭痛
Tingling migraine.
あたしったら
As for me...
競争社会不適合者？ でも挙動は適合者
Unfit for a competitive society? But my behavior is fit.
のフリして暴言吐いて うん ヘコんだ これって放送事故？
Pretending to be, and spitting abuse... Hmm, I'm depressed, is this a broadcasting accident?
へいゆー！
Hey you!
会いたくなってしまったな 今夜も
I've come to want to see you again tonight.
自己嫌悪からの脱却
Escape from self-loathing.
悪霊退散成功だ 嗚呼 異常者なんとか
Exorcism was a success, Ah, someone do something about this crazy person.
頑張れ私 負けるな！
Do your best, me! Don't lose!
せーの
One, two!
好きになっちゃったって言っちゃったって 全然可愛くない
Even if I say I've fallen in love, it's not cute at all.
勝手に凹んだって泣いてみたって 全然可愛くない
Even if I get depressed or try to cry, it's not cute at all.
君だって同じ ダメよりの人種です
You're the same, a hopeless kind of person.
どんだけ優しくするの...？ 私のこと好きなの確定！
How kind are you going to be...? It's confirmed that you like me!
もうこんな時間 どんな予感 神ハプニング
It's already this time, what a premonition, a god-tier happening.
ええ？
Eh?
ああ中毒症状 依存度マックス メンタル崩壊
Ah, addiction symptoms, dependency max, mental breakdown.
あなたのことを もっともっと知りたい
I want to know more and more about you.
ああ 特別じゃない 私のこと
Ah, I'm nothing special, regarding me,
勘違いして...
you've got the wrong idea...
馬鹿ね... なれあいこそが
Don't be silly... This closeness is exactly
君と僕を 繋ぐ光
the light that connects you and me.
月火水木金土日さ 365日
Mon, Tue, Wed, Thu, Fri, Sat, Sun - 365 days.
画面越し ご挨拶
Greetings through the screen.
にゃっはろー！
Nyahallo!
せーの
One, two!
好きになっちゃったって言っちゃったって 全然可愛くない
Even if I say I've fallen in love, it's not cute at all.
勝手に凹んだって泣いてみたって 全然可愛くない 君だって同じ...
Even if I get depressed or try to cry, it's not cute at all. You're the same...
あなたのことを もっともっと知りたい mh...
I want to know more and more about you... mh...
私のことも もっともっと知って欲しい ah...
I want you to know more and more about me too... ah...
あなたのことを 何にも知らない
I don't know anything about you.
Kiss me baby
みこちゃん、誕生日おめでとう！
Miko-chan, Happy Birthday!
ありがとうございました。
Thank you very much.
あ、帰るの早っ。
Ah, you're leaving so fast.
はーい！みんな、ゲストパートどうだった？
Hi! Everyone, how was the guest part?
そして、新衣装お披露目しましたー！どう？
And, I've revealed my new outfit! How is it?
可愛いでしょ。えへへ。あのね、ちょっとね、デート服風に、今回はしました。
It's cute, right? Ehehe. You see, I made it a bit like a date outfit this time.
きゅんきゅん！きゅん！これも完全にきゅんきゅんですねー。
Kyun kyun! Kyun! This is also completely kyun-kyun.
はい、みんなスクショしていいよ。はい。
Yes, everyone, you can take screenshots. Here.
はい！ということで残すところあと1曲となりました！が、その前に告知をしたいと思います！
Yes! So, there's only one song left! But before that, I'd like to make an announcement!
まずはこちら！さくらみこ誕生日記念2024フルセットはこちらとなります！
First, this! The Sakura Miko Birthday Celebration 2024 full set is right here!
はーい！とっても可愛いですね。それでは、単体で見ていきましょう！まずはこちら！
Yes! It's very cute. Now, let's look at them individually! First, this!
みこちと35Pの記念写真アクリルジオラマスタンド！イラストは、おるだん先生に描いていただきました。ありがとう！
The commemorative photo acrylic diorama stand of Mikochi and 35P! The illustration was drawn by Ordan-sensei. Thank you!
おなじみのきゅんポーズでしております。あと35Pもね、プププッっといつものようにおりますね。はい。
I'm doing the familiar kyun pose. And the 35P are there as usual, too. Yes.
では続いてこちら！35Pふわふわキーホルダー！
Now, next is this! 35P fluffy keychain!
みこPがね、とってももふもふとなっております。
MikoP is super fluffy.
そしてこの金の金具のところはね、
And this gold metal part...
この新衣装のこのハートのマークになっております。
is shaped like the heart from my new outfit.
新衣装要素が入ってます。可愛い！
It's got elements of the new outfit. So cute!
はい。では続いては、ドーン！
Alright, next is... Ta-da!
2WAY痛バ For 35P。
2WAY Itabag for 35P.
みこP用の痛バができました！
An itabag for MikoP is finally here!
さっきのね、ふわふわのみこPを付けたりだとか、
You can attach the fluffy MikoP from earlier...
あとポケットにはね、えっとみこのぬいぐるみが2匹くらい入る大きさとなっております。
and the pocket is big enough to fit about two of Miko's plushies.
まああとは缶バッジとかね、いろんなみこのグッズを入れてアピールしてください。
Also, put in can badges and other Miko goods to show them off.
2WAYなのでね、リュックにもなります。
Since it's 2WAY, it can also be a backpack.
あとはまあ、誕生日月同じ、誕生日月の誰かとお揃いかもな。分かんないけど。
And maybe you'll be matching with someone born in the same birthday month. I don't know though.
はい。匂わせしておきます。
Yes. I'll just leave that hint there.
はい。では続いてはこちら。
Alright, next up is this.
35Pキャップ！
The 35P Cap!
もうとってもね、おしゃれになっております。
It's become very fashionable.
コーデュロイ生地っていうのがよく分かんない、あのおしゃれな生地です。
It uses corduroy fabric... I don't really know what that is, but it's a fancy fabric.
そして、みこPの服従のマークがついたりとか、
And, it has the MikoP obedience mark...
みこPのしっぽの炎が後ろに刺繍されております。おしゃれ！
and the flame from MikoP's tail is embroidered on the back. So stylish!
ぜひね、イベントにつけてきてね。
Please wear it to events!
はい。そしてフルセット購入特典はこちら。
Alright. And the full set purchase bonus is this.
おるだん先生の、え、みこの表情差分のイラストに、
An illustration with Miko expression variants by Orudan-sensei...
直筆メッセージと箔押し複製サインが入っております。
with a handwritten message and a foil-stamped reproduction sign.
こちらが数量限定となっております。
This one is limited quantity.
みんなね、急いで頑張って購入してください。
Everyone, please hurry and try your best to buy it.
よろしくお願いします。あはは。
Thank you. Ahaha.
そして、誕生日記念フルセットにはちゃんとこちらもね、
And, the Birthday Celebration Full Set also has...
あの複製のサインとメッセージが入っておりますので。
a reproduction sign and message in it.
みんな買い逃してもぜひね、諦めないで、
Even if you missed out, please don't give up...
あのぜひ全部ゲットしてほしいな、と思います。
and I hope you get everything.
そしてフルセット共通特典、ボイスもついてきます。
And as a common bonus for the full set, it comes with a voice track.
みことみこPの内緒のデートボイスドラマ。
Miko and MikoP's Secret Date voice drama.
ちょっとね、もう珍しいんですけど、ちょっと恥ずかしいんですけど、
It's a bit rare, and a bit embarrassing...
まあデート衣装なんでね。みんなぜひ買って聞いてください。
but it's the date outfit after all. Everyone, please buy and listen to it.
続いての告知はこちら。
The next announcement is this.
鳴門鯛焼本舗さんとのコラボも実施中です！
A collaboration with Naruto Taiyaki Honpo is also underway!
今月末までです。みんな食べに行ってね！
It's until the end of this month. Everyone, go and eat some!
はい。ということで、まだもう一つ告知があります。
Alright. With that, there's still one more announcement.
この後、新曲もお披露目します！イエーイ！
After this, I'll be premiering a new song! Yay!
作詞作曲は木下さんにお願いしました。
I asked Kinoshita-san to write and compose it.
この後MVのプレミア公開もあります。ぜひ見てね！
The MV premiere will follow. Please check it out!
さらに、その後はメンバーシップ限定のライブ＆撮影会もあるので、
Furthermore, after that, there's a membership-only live and photoshoot session...
みんなメンバーさんになってね！
so everyone, please become a member!
あ、なってね！よろしくね。
Oh, please join! Thank you.
さくら組になっていいんだよ！
It's okay to join the Sakuragumi!
はい。それではお待たせいたしました。
Alright. Then, thank you for waiting.
最後の曲になります。
It's time for the final song.
それでは聴いてください。新曲、きゅんきゅんみこきゅんきゅん！
Please listen to it. The new song, Kyun Kyun Miko Kyun Kyun!
いくよ！
Here we go!
きゅんきゅんみこきゅん？
Kyun kyun Miko kyun?
(きゅんきゅんみこきゅん！)
(Kyun kyun Miko kyun!)
きゅんきゅんみこきゅん？
Kyun kyun Miko kyun?
(きゅんきゅんみこきゅん！)
(Kyun kyun Miko kyun!)
きゅんきゅんみこきゅん？
Kyun kyun Miko kyun?
(きゅんきゅんみこきゅん！)
(Kyun kyun Miko kyun!)
きゅんきゅんみこきゅん？ きゅん！
Kyun kyun Miko kyun? Kyun!
キミにみこきゅん？
Miko kyun for you?
ねぇねぇ あのね これガチ
Hey hey, you know what? This is for real.
みんなトモダチ
Everyone is a friend.
夢見るカタチ
A shape of dreaming.
でっかいきってまじ！？
Is a big wish for real!?
まじ～！？
Seriously!?
それはすなわち 成長中ってハナシ
That is to say, we're talking about growing up.
いろんな私 超見て欲しー！
I want you to see all the different sides of me so much!
エリートあいさつ！
Elite Greeting!
みんなー！にゃっはろー！
Everyone! Nyahallo!
エリートスマイル！
Elite Smile!
わっはっはー！
Wah-hah-hah!
エリートダンス！
Elite Dance!
みーみーみこみこみこ！
Mi-mi-mikomikomiko!
エリートイングリッシュ！
Elite English!
I'll be back!
まあ時にはね 落ち込んじゃうこともあるよ
Well, sometimes you might feel down.
そんな時は はなまるあげるにぇ！
In times like those, I'll give you a gold star!
おまえら よく聞けーーーっ！！！
Listen up, you guys!!!
今日も一日よくできました～！
You did great today too~!
ぱにゃてぱにゃてぱにゃっと混ぜたら
Panya-te panya-te panya-tto, once mixed...
きゅんしちゃうかもみこきゅん！
I might just fall in love, Miko kyun!
みこきゅん！
Miko kyun!
ぱにゃてぱにってぱにゃったらサイキョー！！！
Panya-te panya-te panya-ttara, the strongest!!!
うにゃうにゃしよう？
Let's play around?
いっしょに いっしょに
Together, together.
せーの！
One, two!
ドキドキめらめらきゅん！
Doki doki mera mera kyun!
ぴょこぴょこめらめらきゅん！
Pyoko pyoko mera mera kyun!
キラキラめらめらきゅん！
Kira kira mera mera kyun!
きゅんきゅんみこきゅん！
Kyun kyun Miko kyun!
キミにきゅんをあげるよ
I'll give you a "kyun".
ねね！
Hey, hey!
あのね これガチ
Hey, this is for real
ほっぺはモチモチ
Cheeks are soft and squishy
未来のみかち
Future Mikachi
すっごい超トモチ
Super duper besties
それはすなわち
That is to say,
マシュトピ話
A marshmallow-y talk
それは必見だし
It's a must-see
超見て欲しー！
I really want you to see it!
エリート拍手
Elite applause
パチパチパチパチ
Clap clap clap clap
エリートジャンプ
Elite jump
ぴょんぴょんぴょんぴょん
Boing boing boing boing
エリートおねね
Elite sleepy-time
ねんねんねんねん
Sleep sleep sleep sleep
エリートわがまま
Elite selfishness
やだやだやだやだ
No no no no
だっていったって ありのままを伝えたいの
Even so, I want to tell you the truth
おまえらさあ、みこをなめてんじゃねー！！
You guys, don't underestimate Miko!!
ふざけんじゃねえぞーっ！！！！
Don't mess around!!!!
...って言えって言われましたーっ！！ (i_i)
...I was told to say that!! (i_i)
ほにゃって ほにゃって ほにゃっと混ぜたら
Honyatte, honyatte, mixed with a honyat
きゅんしちゃうから みこちゅーん
You'll fall in love, so Miko Tune
ほにゃって ぽにって ぽよったら天才
Honyatte, ponitte, poyotta-ing is a genius
うにゃうにゃしててもいいじゃない
It's okay to be all unya-unya
せーの！
One, two!
ピカピカめろめろきゅん
Sparkling, madly in love, heart-throbbing
ふわふわめろめろきゅん
Fluffy, madly in love, heart-throbbing
みなみなめろめろきゅん
Everyone, madly in love, heart-throbbing
きゅん きゅん みこきゅんきゅん
Kyun kyun Miko kyun kyun
この今が宝物
This moment right now is a treasure
いつも愛をありがとう
Thank you always for your love
ここからはね みこのターン
From here on, it's Miko's turn
ついてきてね！
Keep up with me!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
うーいぇい！
Woo-yay!
いつまでも いつまでも ずっとずっと
Forever and ever, always and always
笑顔でいようね みこ頑張るよ
Let's keep smiling, Miko will do her best
頑張れるよ！
I can do it!
もっと もっと きゅんになってね！
Fall in love more and more!
ラストにもう一回張り切ってー！
One last time, let's get fired up!
みこちゃんはー？
And Miko-chan is—?
エリートです！！
She's an elite!!
ほにゃって ほにゃって ほにゃっと混ぜたら
Honyatte, honyatte, mixed with a honyat
きゅんしちゃうから みこちゅーん
You'll fall in love, so Miko Tune
ほにゃって ぽにって ぽよったら最強
Honyatte, ponitte, poyotta-ing is the strongest
うにゃうにゃしようよ一緒に
Let's be all unya-unya together
せーの！
One, two!
ドキドキめろめろきゅん
Pounding heart, madly in love, heart-throbbing
ひょこひょこめろめろきゅん
Peeking, madly in love, heart-throbbing
キラキラめろめろきゅん
Sparkling, madly in love, heart-throbbing
きゅん きゅん みこきゅんきゅん
Kyun kyun Miko kyun kyun
君にきゅんをあげるよ
I'll give you a heart-throb
みんな！ おつみこー！
Everyone! Otsu Miko-!
そんなときは はなまる あげるにぇ！
In times like that, I'll give you a gold star!
おまえら よく聞けー
You guys, listen up
今日一日 よくできました〜！
You did a great job today~!
ほにゃって ほにゃって ほにゃっと混ぜたら きゅんしちゃうから 35チューン
Honyatte, honyatte, mixed with a honyat, you'll fall in love, so 35 Tune
このあと22時 プレミア公開
Premiering at 22:00 after this
特報！ 3ヶ月連続リリース決定！！！
Breaking News! 3-month consecutive releases decided!!!